galaxyvisions.com 2003-10-03

# Galaxy Visions

GalaxyVisions.com, Inc., the owner of this website, has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.GalaxyVisions.com. 

HOW WE USE IP ADDRESSES  
An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers \-- the big computers that "serve up" Web pages -- automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When guests request pages from GalaxyVisions.com  sites, our servers log the guests' IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. GalaxyVisions.com, Inc. collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart. 

USE OF COOKIES   
What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for customers by saving their passwords, purchases, and preferences while they're at our site. The use of cookies is an industry standard \-- you'll find them at most major Web sites. By showing how and when guests use a site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Cookies are also required for customers to enjoy the Try It On™ feature. A cookie lets the computers remember that you've registered, which allows us to speed up your future activities at our sites. Similarly, GalaxyVisions.com, Inc. uses a temporary cookie to track which products you've chosen to purchase while shopping. The cookie expires once you're done shopping. Letting it do the record keeping saves you the trouble of entering information over and over again during a single visit. If you decline this cookie, you may have difficulty ordering your selections. GalaxyVisions.com, Inc. never uses cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. GalaxyVisions.com, Inc. does not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties whatsoever. GalaxyVisions.com, Inc. does not use cookies to identify specific individuals, except in such cases as online shopping (see above). Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the site, such as the shopping area, will not function properly if you do so. 

LINKS TO OTHER SITES  
Users should be aware that when they are on GalaxyVisions.com, Inc. sites they could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from GalaxyVisions.com, Inc. sites that take you outside our service. For example, if you click on a link to an eye health-related site, the click takes you off the GalaxyVisions.com, Inc. site. This includes links from sponsors and partners that may use GalaxyVisions.com, Inc.'s logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up. We cannot be responsible for your security on sites that are linked to ours. 

INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
We collect several kinds of information from customers and Associates. All of the information we collect can be managed by the customer, meaning that the customer may enter their private area of the site at any time and change or delete their information. For example, we provide the convenience of securely storing credit card information for customer, but this is not a requirement to use the site or to purchase items. A customer can also select or deselect the notification options at will. All of the information we collect we use to enhance and improve a customer's shopping experience, to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

We do not share any of your information with third parties without your permission. During the registration process, you may grant permission for us to share your contact and profile information with third parties or sponsors, generally companies which sell consumer products and services about which our users may be interested. The option for granting this permission is clearly marked on the registration pages. We may also provide you with opportunities at other times to receive information about additional products and services, but we will never share your information with third parties unless you grant us permission to do so. If you grant us permission to share your information with third parties, and then change your mind, you may revoke your permission by entering the "My Details" area and changing the appropriate areas. Because we want our users to feel completely comfortable using the GalaxyVisions.com, Inc. services, we provide you with various opportunities to control how the information you provide to us is used. This site gives users the following options to cancel our service and not receive future communications from us, direct that we not share their information with third parties (in cases where users previously granted us permission to share such information - we do not share users' personal information with third parties without their permission), have us remove their information from our database, and change their profile information.

To request that we not share your personal information with third parties (in cases where you previously granted us permission to share such information - we do not share your personal information with third parties without your permission), or to have all your personal information removed from our database, you can send an e-mail to never@GalaxyVisions.com. The request will be honored as soon as we receive it, but does not affect any information which you provided to us and which we shared with third parties prior to our receipt of such request. If you would like to change any of your profile formation in our database, you can do so by entering the "My Details" area in the website, and following the directions. This will automatically change the information contained in our database. We provide reports to a limited number of companies with which we do business. These reports include aggregate information about our users. The information in these reports will not identify you individually. The outside companies who receive these reports will not be able to contact you from the information contained in the reports. We will not provide individual information to these companies without your permission. 

The website has the ability to collect information in numerous places. All of the information that we request enables us to improve the shopping experience for our customers. 

We never collect information for the purpose of reselling it.OPTIONAL AND MANDATORY INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
Anyplace in the site that requests information we indicate whether the information is mandatory. Customers have the capability to buy products from us without having cookies enabled, and any address and credit card information we collect will be deleted as soon as the order has been fulfilled. 

SECURITY  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. You information is stored on servers that are wholly owned and controlled by GalaxyVisions.com, Inc. 

Access to your information is limited to certain employees of and contractors to GalaxyVisions.com, Inc., all of whom have signed detailed confidentiality agreements regarding the access and use of customer information.   
  
WHEN WE CONTACT CUSTOMERS  
In addition to the communications described below in "Choice/Opt-Out" we send email to customers to 

1) confirm that we have received an order, and

2) confirm that we have shipped their order. If the item is backordered, we will send an email explaining the problem, provide an estimated ship date, and ask if the customer would like to cancel or change the order. 

CHOICE/OPT-OUT  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. If you do not want further communications from us and are unsure whether your information has been removed from our database, you can contact us at [customerservice@galaxyvisions.com](mailto:customerservice@galaxyvisions.com). We will be sure that you will not receive future communications or no longer receive our services. 

PRIVACY STATEMENT CHANGES  
From time to time we may alter our practices, or add new practices, regarding privacy issues. Whenever a change is made, we will update this privacy statement to reflect the change. Please be sure to check our statement periodically to stay current on these practices. 

CONTACTING THE WEB SITE  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, You can Contact. [webmaster@galaxyvisions.com](mailto:webmaster@galaxyvisions.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy)
